[
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "I%20________%20go%20to%20New%20York%20this%20autumn.",
    "correct_answer": "am%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "to%20be%20going%20to",
      "am%20going%20to",
      "isn’t%20going%20to",
      "are%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Mary%20_____%20have%20a%20baby%20this%20summer.",
    "correct_answer":"is%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "am%20going%20to",
      "is%20going%20to",
      "are%20going%20to",
      "am%20not%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "My%20bestie%20%20_____%20%20join%20us%20this%20Saturday,%20her%20babies%20are%20sick.",
    "correct_answer": "Isn’t%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Isn’t%20going%20to",
      "Are%20going%20to",
      "Am%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "We%20____%20drive%20there,%20our%20relatives%20need%20us!%20Not%20a%20word%20any%20more!%20Go%20get%20your%20stuff!",
    "correct_answer": "Are%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Isn’t%20going%20to",
      "Are%20going%20to",
      "Aren’t%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Daniel%20and%20Mark%20_______%20%20%20be%20a%20little%20bit%20later.%20Let’s%20wait%20for%20them.",
    "correct_answer": "Are%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Isn’t%20going%20to",
      "Are%20going%20to",
      "Aren’t%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "We%20_____%20%20move%20the%20house%20this%20week.%20So%20I%20have%20no%20free%20time,%20sorry.",
    "correct_answer": "Are%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Isn’t%20going%20to",
      "Are%20going%20to",
      "Aren’t%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "_______%20sign%20the%20papers?%20I’m%20still%20waiting.",
    "correct_answer": "Are%20you%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Is%20you%20going%20to",
      "Are%20you%20going%20to",
      "Am%20she%20going%20to",
      "Who%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Oh,%20it%20__________%20snow%20now…%20I%20hate%20snowy%20and%20cloudy%20weather!",
    "correct_answer": "Is%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Am%20going%20to",
      "is%20not%20going%20to",
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Are%20going%20to"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The%20player%20______%20leave%20the%20team%20this%20April.",
    "correct_answer": "Is%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Are%20going%20to",
      "Is%20going%20to",
      "Am%20going%20to",
      "Is%20going"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "To%20be%20going%20to",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The%20sales%20manager%20______%20offer%20the%20best%20options%20for%20you!",
    "correct_answer": "is%20going%20to",
    "answers": [
      "Am%20going%20to",
      "is%20going%20to",
      "Is%20going",
      "Are%20going%20to"
    ]
  }
]
